{
  "uniqueId": 36,
  "name": "English Vocabulary Quiz",
  "article": "an",
  "instructions": "Guess the word!",
  "questionCreationStrategy": "TEXT_WITH_HINT",
  "dictionaryLinkStrategy": "WEBSTER_ANSWER",
  "answerTimeLimitStrategy": "WITH_HINT",
  "cardPreprocessingStrategy": "BETTER_ENGLISH_DEFINITIONS",
  "discordFinalAnswerListElementStrategy": "ANSWER_ONLY",
  "scoreAnswerStrategy": "ONE_ANSWER_ONE_POINT",
  "additionalAnswerWaitStrategy": "JAPANESE_SETTINGS",
  "discordIntermediateAnswerListElementStrategy": "CORRECT_ANSWERS",
  "cards": [
    {
      "question": "uncontrolled motion that is irregular or unpredictable",
      "answer": "errant"
    },
    {
      "question": "part of a dress above the waist  ",
      "answer": "bodice"
    },
    {
      "question": "the quality of being final or definitely settled",
      "answer": "finality"
    },
    {
      "question": "an offensive term for a Black nursemaid in the southern U.S.  ",
      "answer": "mammy"
    },
    {
      "question": "occurring or coming into existence after a person's death",
      "answer": "posthumous"
    },
    {
      "question": "(used of foods) preserved in a pickling liquid  ",
      "answer": "pickled"
    },
    {
      "question": "(United Kingdom) a written statement of the grounds of complaint made to court of law asking for the grievance to be redressed  ",
      "answer": "plaint"
    },
    {
      "question": "pigeon that executes backward somersaults in flight or on the ground  ",
      "answer": "roller"
    },
    {
      "question": "in a signal manner",
      "answer": "signally"
    },
    {
      "question": "not obtrusive or undesirably noticeable",
      "answer": "unobtrusive"
    },
    {
      "question": "the determination of the actual temporal sequence of past events  ",
      "answer": "chronology"
    },
    {
      "question": "furnish with a cornice  ",
      "answer": "cornice"
    },
    {
      "question": "recitation of a speech from memory with studied gestures and intonation as an exercise in elocution or rhetoric  ",
      "answer": "declamation"
    },
    {
      "question": "rigorous self-denial and active self-restraint  ",
      "answer": "asceticism"
    },
    {
      "question": "desire for sensual pleasures  ",
      "answer": "sensuality"
    },
    {
      "question": "a large entrance or reception room or area  ",
      "answer": "anteroom"
    },
    {
      "question": "terminate or abbreviate before its intended or proper end or its full extent",
      "answer": "clip"
    },
    {
      "question": "not being under control",
      "answer": "uncontrolled"
    },
    {
      "question": "of or characteristic of or occurring in spring",
      "answer": "vernal"
    },
    {
      "question": "with admiration",
      "answer": "admiringly"
    },
    {
      "question": "the act of propelling with force  ",
      "answer": "launching"
    },
    {
      "question": "supply sparingly and with restricted quantities",
      "answer": "stint"
    },
    {
      "question": "process of changing to an inferior state  ",
      "answer": "deterioration"
    },
    {
      "question": "an indirect (and usually malicious) implication  ",
      "answer": "insinuation"
    },
    {
      "question": "(of meat) full of sinews",
      "answer": "fibrous"
    },
    {
      "question": "an imperfection or defectiveness",
      "answer": "lameness"
    },
    {
      "question": "a twilled woolen fabric  ",
      "answer": "serge"
    },
    {
      "question": "characteristic of spectacles or drama",
      "answer": "spectacular"
    },
    {
      "question": "an elementary book summarizing the principles of a Christian religion",
      "answer": "catechism"
    },
    {
      "question": "informal term for information",
      "answer": "gen"
    },
    {
      "question": "do away with  ",
      "answer": "obviate"
    },
    {
      "question": "give supporting evidence",
      "answer": "vouch"
    },
    {
      "question": "a person of authority who subjects others to undue pressures  ",
      "answer": "oppressor"
    },
    {
      "question": "a low seat or a stool to rest the feet of a seated person  ",
      "answer": "footstool"
    },
    {
      "question": "to an undeniable degree or in an undeniable manner",
      "answer": "undeniably"
    },
    {
      "question": "in a demure manner",
      "answer": "demurely"
    },
    {
      "question": "a channel for communication between groups",
      "answer": "liaison"
    },
    {
      "question": "not closed or secured",
      "answer": "unfastened"
    },
    {
      "question": "without or almost without hope",
      "answer": "despondent"
    },
    {
      "question": "a grammatical category in inflected languages governing the agreement between nouns and pronouns and adjectives",
      "answer": "gender"
    },
    {
      "question": "a grammatical number category referring to two items or units as opposed to one item (singular) or more than two items (plural)",
      "answer": "dual"
    },
    {
      "question": "attach to  ",
      "answer": "annex"
    },
    {
      "question": "the act of retaining something  ",
      "answer": "retention"
    },
    {
      "question": "make useful again",
      "answer": "reclaim"
    },
    {
      "question": "in or of the month preceding the present one",
      "answer": "ultimo"
    },
    {
      "question": "a standard or typical example",
      "answer": "prototype"
    },
    {
      "question": "a public performer (a dancer or singer)  ",
      "answer": "artiste"
    },
    {
      "question": "not frequent",
      "answer": "infrequent"
    },
    {
      "question": "not perceived or commented on  ",
      "answer": "unperceived"
    },
    {
      "question": "guilt as an accomplice in a crime or offense  ",
      "answer": "complicity"
    },
    {
      "question": "a building designed and equipped to observe astronomical phenomena  ",
      "answer": "observatory"
    },
    {
      "question": "poor and often mischievous city child  ",
      "answer": "urchin"
    },
    {
      "question": "someone who conducts a statistical survey  ",
      "answer": "surveyor"
    },
    {
      "question": "(microbiology) single-celled or noncellular spherical or spiral or rod-shaped organisms lacking chlorophyll that reproduce by fission",
      "answer": "bacteria"
    },
    {
      "question": "border consisting of anything placed on the edge to finish something (such as a fringe on clothing or on a rug)  ",
      "answer": "edging"
    },
    {
      "question": "the facility where wild animals are housed for exhibition  ",
      "answer": "menagerie"
    },
    {
      "question": "sink down or precipitate",
      "answer": "subside"
    },
    {
      "question": "returning to health after illness or debility",
      "answer": "convalescent"
    },
    {
      "question": "examine physically with or as if with a probe",
      "answer": "probe"
    },
    {
      "question": "in keeping with the season",
      "answer": "seasonable"
    },
    {
      "question": "a broad range of related objects or values or qualities or ideas or activities  ",
      "answer": "spectrum"
    },
    {
      "question": "having horns or hornlike projections",
      "answer": "horny"
    },
    {
      "question": "a room (as in a residence) containing a bathtub or shower and usually a washbasin and toilet  ",
      "answer": "bathroom"
    },
    {
      "question": "an old name for sulfur  ",
      "answer": "brimstone"
    },
    {
      "question": "the sport of gliding on skates  ",
      "answer": "skating"
    },
    {
      "question": "relating to or interested in sports  ",
      "answer": "sportive"
    },
    {
      "question": "the remaining parts of something that has been wrecked",
      "answer": "wreckage"
    },
    {
      "question": "a craftsman who works with stone or brick  ",
      "answer": "mason"
    },
    {
      "question": "a system for classifying things into groups  ",
      "answer": "grouping"
    },
    {
      "question": "someone who acts speaks or writes in an amusing way  ",
      "answer": "humorist"
    },
    {
      "question": "the branch of social science that deals with the production and distribution and consumption of goods and services and their management  ",
      "answer": "economics"
    },
    {
      "question": "the study or investigation of ancestry and family history  ",
      "answer": "genealogy"
    },
    {
      "question": "provoke or stir up",
      "answer": "incite"
    },
    {
      "question": "a body of troops in close array  ",
      "answer": "phalanx"
    },
    {
      "question": "with regret (used in polite formulas)",
      "answer": "regretfully"
    },
    {
      "question": "vulgar or irreverent speech or action  ",
      "answer": "profanity"
    },
    {
      "question": "having the color of a canary",
      "answer": "canary"
    },
    {
      "question": "conscientious attention to rules and details  ",
      "answer": "strictness"
    },
    {
      "question": "giving spirit and vivacity  ",
      "answer": "animating"
    },
    {
      "question": "form vertical ribs by knitting",
      "answer": "rib"
    },
    {
      "question": "fight or struggle in a confused way at close quarters",
      "answer": "scuffle"
    },
    {
      "question": "(used of sums of money) so small in amount as to deserve contempt  ",
      "answer": "beggarly"
    },
    {
      "question": "a political system governed by a few people",
      "answer": "oligarchy"
    },
    {
      "question": "a swaggering show of courage  ",
      "answer": "bravado"
    },
    {
      "question": "lacking any legal or binding force",
      "answer": "null"
    },
    {
      "question": "a circularity that has a different center or deviates from a circular path  ",
      "answer": "eccentricity"
    },
    {
      "question": "the act of atoning for sin or wrongdoing (especially appeasing a deity)  ",
      "answer": "expiation"
    },
    {
      "question": "make peace with  ",
      "answer": "propitiate"
    },
    {
      "question": "having or showing or conforming to good taste  ",
      "answer": "tasteful"
    },
    {
      "question": "a final peremptory demand  ",
      "answer": "ultimatum"
    },
    {
      "question": "likely to change frequently often without apparent or cogent reason",
      "answer": "inconstant"
    },
    {
      "question": "stiff cardboard made by pasting together layers of paper  ",
      "answer": "pasteboard"
    },
    {
      "question": "with respect to the economic system",
      "answer": "economically"
    },
    {
      "question": "sweet usually dark purple blackberry-like fruit of any of several mulberry trees of the genus Morus  ",
      "answer": "mulberry"
    },
    {
      "question": "the quality of being clear and transparent  ",
      "answer": "transparency"
    },
    {
      "question": "relating to a small administrative district or community",
      "answer": "communal"
    },
    {
      "question": "giving sexual pleasure",
      "answer": "erotic"
    },
    {
      "question": "an object perceived during a hallucinatory episode",
      "answer": "hallucination"
    },
    {
      "question": "a heavy woolen fabric with a long nap  ",
      "answer": "frieze"
    },
    {
      "question": "botfly larva",
      "answer": "bot"
    },
    {
      "question": "causing mental discomfort",
      "answer": "disquieting"
    },
    {
      "question": "cost accounting  ",
      "answer": "costing"
    },
    {
      "question": "infectious",
      "answer": "virulent"
    },
    {
      "question": "an ostentatious and inappropriate display of learning  ",
      "answer": "pedantry"
    },
    {
      "question": "secretly importing prohibited goods or goods on which duty is due  ",
      "answer": "smuggling"
    },
    {
      "question": "a county jail that holds prisoners for periods up to 18 months  ",
      "answer": "workhouse"
    },
    {
      "question": "an electronic device for producing a signal voltage  ",
      "answer": "generator"
    },
    {
      "question": "characterized by unrest or disorder",
      "answer": "unquiet"
    },
    {
      "question": "a noblewoman ranking below a duchess and above a countess  ",
      "answer": "marchioness"
    },
    {
      "question": "an evergreen tree  ",
      "answer": "hemlock"
    },
    {
      "question": "a person with the same name as another  ",
      "answer": "namesake"
    },
    {
      "question": "identifying the nature or cause of some phenomenon  ",
      "answer": "diagnosis"
    },
    {
      "question": "curved down like an eagle's beak  ",
      "answer": "aquiline"
    },
    {
      "question": "a feeling of sympathy and sorrow for the misfortunes of others",
      "answer": "commiseration"
    },
    {
      "question": "young of any of various fur-bearing animals",
      "answer": "kit"
    },
    {
      "question": "the tendency to float in water or other liquid  ",
      "answer": "buoyancy"
    },
    {
      "question": "suffering shame  ",
      "answer": "discredited"
    },
    {
      "question": "a particularly difficult or baffling question or problem  ",
      "answer": "poser"
    },
    {
      "question": "extremely conservative  ",
      "answer": "reactionary"
    },
    {
      "question": "without revealing one's identity",
      "answer": "incognito"
    },
    {
      "question": "divide into cantons, of a country  ",
      "answer": "canton"
    },
    {
      "question": "an aptitude that may be developed  ",
      "answer": "capability"
    },
    {
      "question": "not injured  ",
      "answer": "unharmed"
    },
    {
      "question": "related to or characterized by or given to atheism",
      "answer": "atheist"
    },
    {
      "question": "black-and-red or black-and-yellow orioles of the American tropics  ",
      "answer": "cacique"
    },
    {
      "question": "without need",
      "answer": "needlessly"
    },
    {
      "question": "any of numerous short-stemmed plants of the genus Primula having tufted basal leaves and showy flowers clustered in umbels or heads  ",
      "answer": "primrose"
    },
    {
      "question": "make a snorting sound by exhaling hard",
      "answer": "snort"
    },
    {
      "question": "a hypothetical possibility, circumstance, statement, proposal, situation, etc.",
      "answer": "hypothetical"
    },
    {
      "question": "having odor or a characteristic odor",
      "answer": "odorous"
    },
    {
      "question": "put (something somewhere) firmly",
      "answer": "situate"
    },
    {
      "question": "not in keeping with (and usually undesirable for) the season",
      "answer": "unseasonable"
    },
    {
      "question": "revealed",
      "answer": "unveiled"
    },
    {
      "question": "one who accompanies and supervises a young woman or gatherings of young people  ",
      "answer": "chaperon"
    },
    {
      "question": "in a wasteful manner",
      "answer": "extravagantly"
    },
    {
      "question": "the quality of disagreeing",
      "answer": "incongruity"
    },
    {
      "question": "the quality of being sacred  ",
      "answer": "sacredness"
    },
    {
      "question": "contemplation of things past",
      "answer": "retrospect"
    },
    {
      "question": "a conceited dandy who is overly impressed by his own accomplishments  ",
      "answer": "coxcomb"
    },
    {
      "question": "habitual mode of behavior  ",
      "answer": "habitude"
    },
    {
      "question": "lacking even the rudiments of courage",
      "answer": "craven"
    },
    {
      "question": "in three month intervals",
      "answer": "quarterly"
    },
    {
      "question": "gold or silver in bars or ingots  ",
      "answer": "bullion"
    },
    {
      "question": "a streak of light in the sky at night that results when a meteoroid hits the earth's atmosphere and air friction causes the meteoroid to melt or vaporize or explode  ",
      "answer": "meteor"
    },
    {
      "question": "represent abstractly, for example in a painting, drawing, or sculpture",
      "answer": "portray"
    },
    {
      "question": "(law) a pleading made by a defendant in response to the plaintiff's replication  ",
      "answer": "rejoinder"
    },
    {
      "question": "instructive (especially excessively)  ",
      "answer": "didactic"
    },
    {
      "question": "shout `hurrah!'  ",
      "answer": "hurrah"
    },
    {
      "question": "strike with a cudgel  ",
      "answer": "cudgel"
    },
    {
      "question": "the dead body of an animal especially one slaughtered and dressed for food  ",
      "answer": "carcase"
    },
    {
      "question": "manifest a sharp increase",
      "answer": "spike"
    },
    {
      "question": "in a vertical direction",
      "answer": "vertically"
    },
    {
      "question": "a person who keeps a devotional vigil by a sick bed or by a dead body  ",
      "answer": "watcher"
    },
    {
      "question": "(used of texts) shortened by condensing or rewriting",
      "answer": "abridged"
    },
    {
      "question": "deceive by a mock action",
      "answer": "feint"
    },
    {
      "question": "of or relating to or caused by the greenhouse effect",
      "answer": "greenhouse"
    },
    {
      "question": "uncastrated adult male horse  ",
      "answer": "stallion"
    },
    {
      "question": "line with beams or planks",
      "answer": "crib"
    },
    {
      "question": "a hollow cylinder passed from runner to runner in a relay race  ",
      "answer": "baton"
    },
    {
      "question": "the murder of a competitor  ",
      "answer": "elimination"
    },
    {
      "question": "so as to be palpable",
      "answer": "palpably"
    },
    {
      "question": "someone who makes charitable donations intended to increase human well-being  ",
      "answer": "philanthropist"
    },
    {
      "question": "a descendent or heir",
      "answer": "scion"
    },
    {
      "question": "a fee paid for instruction (especially for higher education)",
      "answer": "tuition"
    },
    {
      "question": "a person suffering with rheumatism  ",
      "answer": "rheumatic"
    },
    {
      "question": "varying in color when seen in different lights or from different angles",
      "answer": "changeable"
    },
    {
      "question": "moral weakness  ",
      "answer": "frailty"
    },
    {
      "question": "imposing or depending on or containing a condition",
      "answer": "conditional"
    },
    {
      "question": "lacking in correct logical relation  ",
      "answer": "illogical"
    },
    {
      "question": "beat the seeds out of a grain  ",
      "answer": "thrash"
    },
    {
      "question": "an extensive alteration of the structure of a corporation or government",
      "answer": "reorganization"
    },
    {
      "question": "supplied with a vent or vents for intake of air or discharge of gases  ",
      "answer": "vented"
    },
    {
      "question": "a contestant (human or animal) not considered to have a good chance to win  ",
      "answer": "outsider"
    },
    {
      "question": "publicize or announce by placards  ",
      "answer": "placard"
    },
    {
      "question": "spice from dried unopened flower bud of the clove tree",
      "answer": "clove"
    },
    {
      "question": "break from a meeting or gathering",
      "answer": "adjourn"
    },
    {
      "question": "located on or near or bordering on a coast",
      "answer": "coastal"
    },
    {
      "question": "a stick or pin used to twist the yarn in spinning  ",
      "answer": "spindle"
    },
    {
      "question": "interweave with tinsel",
      "answer": "tinsel"
    },
    {
      "question": "a brief abstract (as of an article or book)  ",
      "answer": "epitome"
    },
    {
      "question": "drawn off in the form of vapor",
      "answer": "evaporated"
    },
    {
      "question": "lack of attention  ",
      "answer": "inattention"
    },
    {
      "question": "shout, as if with joy or enthusiasm",
      "answer": "whoop"
    },
    {
      "question": "with the bottom lodged on the ground",
      "answer": "aground"
    },
    {
      "question": "a black garment reaching down to the ankles",
      "answer": "cassock"
    },
    {
      "question": "of or relating to the plant life in a particular region",
      "answer": "floral"
    },
    {
      "question": "make one's debut",
      "answer": "debut"
    },
    {
      "question": "compete with successfully",
      "answer": "emulate"
    },
    {
      "question": "cut off the testicles (of male animals such as horses)",
      "answer": "geld"
    },
    {
      "question": "oval-shaped edible seed of the almond tree  ",
      "answer": "almond"
    },
    {
      "question": "fighting with the fists  ",
      "answer": "boxing"
    },
    {
      "question": "without any delay",
      "answer": "instantaneously"
    },
    {
      "question": "become long or longer",
      "answer": "lengthen"
    },
    {
      "question": "a group of many islands in a large body of water  ",
      "answer": "archipelago"
    },
    {
      "question": "with devotion",
      "answer": "devotedly"
    },
    {
      "question": "characterized by a band of especially white around the body",
      "answer": "banded"
    },
    {
      "question": "not yet mature  ",
      "answer": "immature"
    },
    {
      "question": "marked by low spirits",
      "answer": "dispirited"
    },
    {
      "question": "mustelid of northern hemisphere in its white winter coat  ",
      "answer": "ermine"
    },
    {
      "question": "wishing or appearing to wish evil to others",
      "answer": "malevolent"
    },
    {
      "question": "destroy or damage seriously, as of someone's reputation",
      "answer": "assassinate"
    },
    {
      "question": "a maid who is employed to clean and care for bedrooms (now primarily in hotels)  ",
      "answer": "chambermaid"
    },
    {
      "question": "a person who works in a prison and is in charge of prisoners  ",
      "answer": "warder"
    },
    {
      "question": "a storm with widespread snowfall accompanied by strong winds  ",
      "answer": "blizzard"
    },
    {
      "question": "entering upon a position of office vacated by another",
      "answer": "incoming"
    },
    {
      "question": "small cask or barrel  ",
      "answer": "keg"
    },
    {
      "question": "indulge in fantasies",
      "answer": "fantasy"
    },
    {
      "question": "a statue of a naked human figure  ",
      "answer": "nude"
    },
    {
      "question": "having patronage or clients",
      "answer": "patronized"
    },
    {
      "question": "subdued or overcome",
      "answer": "quelled"
    },
    {
      "question": "building again  ",
      "answer": "rebuilding"
    },
    {
      "question": "unwilling because of mild dislike or disapproval",
      "answer": "disinclined"
    },
    {
      "question": "a serious crime (such as murder or arson)  ",
      "answer": "felony"
    },
    {
      "question": "first in order of birth",
      "answer": "firstborn"
    },
    {
      "question": "criticize or abuse strongly and violently",
      "answer": "rip"
    },
    {
      "question": "any of various spiny trees or shrubs of the genus Acacia  ",
      "answer": "acacia"
    },
    {
      "question": "the dead and rotting body of an animal",
      "answer": "carrion"
    },
    {
      "question": "declare legally insane  ",
      "answer": "certify"
    },
    {
      "question": "the work of a sailor  ",
      "answer": "seafaring"
    },
    {
      "question": "annual or biennial or perennial herbs having showy flowers  ",
      "answer": "poppy"
    },
    {
      "question": "massive powerful herbivorous odd-toed ungulate of southeast Asia and Africa having very thick skin and one or two horns on the snout  ",
      "answer": "rhinoceros"
    },
    {
      "question": "abjectly submissive",
      "answer": "slavish"
    },
    {
      "question": "distill (alcohol) illegally",
      "answer": "moonshine"
    },
    {
      "question": "to a vital degree",
      "answer": "vitally"
    },
    {
      "question": "provide with abilities or understanding",
      "answer": "equip"
    },
    {
      "question": "engage in a rehearsal (of)  ",
      "answer": "rehearse"
    },
    {
      "question": "having long and narrow ornamental cuts showing an underlying fabric",
      "answer": "slashed"
    },
    {
      "question": "recurring in scattered and irregular or unpredictable instances",
      "answer": "sporadic"
    },
    {
      "question": "grow and spread fast",
      "answer": "mushroom"
    },
    {
      "question": "become friends with",
      "answer": "befriend"
    },
    {
      "question": "deeply agitated especially from emotion",
      "answer": "distraught"
    },
    {
      "question": "a large sleeping room containing several beds  ",
      "answer": "dormitory"
    },
    {
      "question": "liquid excretory product",
      "answer": "urine"
    },
    {
      "question": "a detailed explanation of the meaning of something  ",
      "answer": "explication"
    },
    {
      "question": "showing inappropriate levity  ",
      "answer": "flippant"
    },
    {
      "question": "suited to or suggestive of a grave or burial",
      "answer": "funereal"
    },
    {
      "question": "convert into malt  ",
      "answer": "malt"
    },
    {
      "question": "turn sharply",
      "answer": "swerve"
    },
    {
      "question": "having the reason or cause not made clear",
      "answer": "unexplained"
    },
    {
      "question": "the art or practice of writing verse  ",
      "answer": "versification"
    },
    {
      "question": "the termination or destruction of union  ",
      "answer": "disunion"
    },
    {
      "question": "not revering god  ",
      "answer": "godless"
    },
    {
      "question": "absence of moral or spiritual values",
      "answer": "iniquity"
    },
    {
      "question": "deficient in amount or quality or extent",
      "answer": "meager"
    },
    {
      "question": "of or relating to or suitable for statues  ",
      "answer": "statuary"
    },
    {
      "question": "balcony consisting of the forward section of a theater mezzanine  ",
      "answer": "loge"
    },
    {
      "question": "a resin obtained from the camphor tree",
      "answer": "camphor"
    },
    {
      "question": "without substance",
      "answer": "cardboard"
    },
    {
      "question": "a spear thrown as a weapon or in competitive field events  ",
      "answer": "javelin"
    },
    {
      "question": "tangled in knots or snarls",
      "answer": "knotty"
    },
    {
      "question": "a white sparkling wine either produced in Champagne or resembling that produced there  ",
      "answer": "champagne"
    },
    {
      "question": "resistant to physical force or pressure",
      "answer": "unyielding"
    },
    {
      "question": "kill en masse",
      "answer": "exterminate"
    },
    {
      "question": "an accidental happening",
      "answer": "hap"
    },
    {
      "question": "lift up or elevate  ",
      "answer": "uplift"
    },
    {
      "question": "softened by the addition of cushions or padding  ",
      "answer": "cushioned"
    },
    {
      "question": "the quality of being disloyal  ",
      "answer": "disloyalty"
    },
    {
      "question": "the discharge of semen in males  ",
      "answer": "ejaculation"
    },
    {
      "question": "small dried seedless raisin grown in the Mediterranean region and California",
      "answer": "currant"
    },
    {
      "question": "the speech act of answering an attack on your assertions",
      "answer": "refutation"
    },
    {
      "question": "a temporary rank held by young naval officers in training  ",
      "answer": "midshipman"
    },
    {
      "question": "a mechanical system in a building that provides fresh air",
      "answer": "ventilation"
    },
    {
      "question": "a sovereign prince of the former ruling house of Austria  ",
      "answer": "archduke"
    },
    {
      "question": "make revisions in",
      "answer": "revise"
    },
    {
      "question": "memorization by repetition  ",
      "answer": "rote"
    },
    {
      "question": "avoid dealing with",
      "answer": "shirk"
    },
    {
      "question": "an elderly unmarried woman  ",
      "answer": "spinster"
    },
    {
      "question": "without comfort",
      "answer": "comfortless"
    },
    {
      "question": "an artisan who makes jewelry and other objects out of gold  ",
      "answer": "goldsmith"
    },
    {
      "question": "the native habitat or home of an animal or plant  ",
      "answer": "habitation"
    },
    {
      "question": "behave unnaturally or affectedly",
      "answer": "dissemble"
    },
    {
      "question": "do away with completely, without leaving a trace  ",
      "answer": "obliterate"
    },
    {
      "question": "made of wood of the ash tree  ",
      "answer": "ashen"
    },
    {
      "question": "the act of intimidating a weaker person to make them do something  ",
      "answer": "bullying"
    },
    {
      "question": "left-hand page  ",
      "answer": "verso"
    },
    {
      "question": "adjusted to reflect value or proportion",
      "answer": "weighted"
    },
    {
      "question": "a vehicle that can fly  ",
      "answer": "aircraft"
    },
    {
      "question": "the uninflected form of the verb  ",
      "answer": "infinitive"
    },
    {
      "question": "coming next after the twenty-ninth in position  ",
      "answer": "thirtieth"
    },
    {
      "question": "freedom from bias or from selfish motives  ",
      "answer": "disinterestedness"
    },
    {
      "question": "a treatise advancing a new point of view resulting from research",
      "answer": "dissertation"
    },
    {
      "question": "seize or catch with a swooping motion  ",
      "answer": "swoop"
    },
    {
      "question": "root of any of several members of the mustard family  ",
      "answer": "turnip"
    },
    {
      "question": "made less hopeful or enthusiastic",
      "answer": "demoralized"
    },
    {
      "question": "subjected to great tension",
      "answer": "taut"
    },
    {
      "question": "remove or force from a position of dwelling previously occupied",
      "answer": "dislodge"
    },
    {
      "question": "not perceptible to the touch",
      "answer": "impalpable"
    },
    {
      "question": "make impossible, especially beforehand  ",
      "answer": "preclude"
    },
    {
      "question": "supported by evidence",
      "answer": "evidenced"
    },
    {
      "question": "confine as if in a prison",
      "answer": "imprison"
    },
    {
      "question": "in a meditative manner",
      "answer": "meditatively"
    },
    {
      "question": "characterized by an attitude of ready accessibility (especially about one's actions or purposes)",
      "answer": "openness"
    },
    {
      "question": "a mechanical device that rotates to push against air or water  ",
      "answer": "propeller"
    },
    {
      "question": "regularly spaced in time",
      "answer": "timed"
    },
    {
      "question": "conclude by reasoning",
      "answer": "deduce"
    },
    {
      "question": "flamboyantly adventurous  ",
      "answer": "swaggering"
    },
    {
      "question": "make wrinkles or creases on a smooth surface",
      "answer": "wrinkle"
    },
    {
      "question": "a special anniversary (or the celebration of it)  ",
      "answer": "jubilee"
    },
    {
      "question": "(of handwriting, print, etc.) capable of being read or deciphered",
      "answer": "legible"
    },
    {
      "question": "either end of a railroad or bus route  ",
      "answer": "terminus"
    },
    {
      "question": "sew",
      "answer": "tick"
    },
    {
      "question": "moving over territory to search for something",
      "answer": "scouring"
    },
    {
      "question": "established firmly and securely",
      "answer": "entrenched"
    },
    {
      "question": "come into the possession of",
      "answer": "accrue"
    },
    {
      "question": "the market value set on assets  ",
      "answer": "assessment"
    },
    {
      "question": "a shaft on which a wheel rotates  ",
      "answer": "axle"
    },
    {
      "question": "rub hard or scrub",
      "answer": "scour"
    },
    {
      "question": "put together with a seam",
      "answer": "seam"
    },
    {
      "question": "the act of deluding",
      "answer": "delusion"
    },
    {
      "question": "take up the cause, ideology, practice, method, of someone and use it as one's own",
      "answer": "espouse"
    },
    {
      "question": "a child of your son or daughter  ",
      "answer": "grandchild"
    },
    {
      "question": "the act of making something less tight  ",
      "answer": "loosening"
    },
    {
      "question": "make a play on words",
      "answer": "pun"
    },
    {
      "question": "capable of being traced or tracked",
      "answer": "traceable"
    },
    {
      "question": "the system of law courts that administer justice and constitute the judicial branch of government  ",
      "answer": "judiciary"
    },
    {
      "question": "modestly or warily rejecting approaches or overtures",
      "answer": "coy"
    },
    {
      "question": "in a vicious manner",
      "answer": "viciously"
    },
    {
      "question": "generator that extracts usable energy from winds  ",
      "answer": "windmill"
    },
    {
      "question": "power to be effective",
      "answer": "effectiveness"
    },
    {
      "question": "a person who is not a serf or a slave  ",
      "answer": "freeman"
    },
    {
      "question": "not selective of a single class or person",
      "answer": "promiscuous"
    },
    {
      "question": "of or relating to the sequential performance of multiple operations",
      "answer": "serial"
    },
    {
      "question": "used of the back and knees",
      "answer": "bended"
    },
    {
      "question": "of or relating to billiards",
      "answer": "billiard"
    },
    {
      "question": "infinitely or immeasurably small",
      "answer": "infinitesimal"
    },
    {
      "question": "with hand brought forward and up from below shoulder level",
      "answer": "underhand"
    },
    {
      "question": "animation and energy in action or expression",
      "answer": "liveliness"
    },
    {
      "question": "act of cooperating traitorously with an enemy that is occupying your country  ",
      "answer": "collaboration"
    },
    {
      "question": "totally submissive  ",
      "answer": "cringing"
    },
    {
      "question": "(historical linguistics) an explanation of the historical origins of a word or phrase  ",
      "answer": "deriving"
    },
    {
      "question": "keep or store in a garage",
      "answer": "garage"
    },
    {
      "question": "forceful and extreme and rigorous",
      "answer": "drastic"
    },
    {
      "question": "introduce into the body through a vein, for therapeutic purposes",
      "answer": "infuse"
    },
    {
      "question": "used for punishment or reform of criminals or wrongdoers",
      "answer": "penitentiary"
    },
    {
      "question": "a gathering of the minimal number of members of an organization to conduct business  ",
      "answer": "quorum"
    },
    {
      "question": "mark with a buoy  ",
      "answer": "buoy"
    },
    {
      "question": "any vine of the family Cucurbitaceae that bears fruits with hard rinds  ",
      "answer": "gourd"
    },
    {
      "question": "made less severe or intense",
      "answer": "mitigated"
    },
    {
      "question": "convert into slag  ",
      "answer": "slag"
    },
    {
      "question": "made dull or blunt  ",
      "answer": "blunted"
    },
    {
      "question": "a purulent infection at the end of a finger or toe in the area surrounding the nail  ",
      "answer": "felon"
    },
    {
      "question": "in an obscure manner",
      "answer": "obscurely"
    },
    {
      "question": "(astronomy) position of a planet as defined by its angular distance from its perihelion (as observed from the sun)  ",
      "answer": "anomaly"
    },
    {
      "question": "the body of voters who elect a representative for their area  ",
      "answer": "constituency"
    },
    {
      "question": "not belonging to that in which it is contained",
      "answer": "extraneous"
    },
    {
      "question": "having unpredictable ups and downs",
      "answer": "fluctuating"
    },
    {
      "question": "climb mountains for pleasure as a sport  ",
      "answer": "mountaineer"
    },
    {
      "question": "(military) signal to turn the lights out  ",
      "answer": "taps"
    },
    {
      "question": "volatile liquid distilled from turpentine oleoresin",
      "answer": "turpentine"
    },
    {
      "question": "(used of hooves) split, divided",
      "answer": "cloven"
    },
    {
      "question": "neurotic disorder characterized by violent emotional outbreaks and disturbances of sensory and motor functions  ",
      "answer": "hysteria"
    },
    {
      "question": "of or relating to or characteristic of members of the family Canidae  ",
      "answer": "canine"
    },
    {
      "question": "someone who spends money prodigally  ",
      "answer": "spendthrift"
    },
    {
      "question": "inequality or difference in some respect  ",
      "answer": "disparity"
    },
    {
      "question": "the trait of being agreeably submissive and manageable  ",
      "answer": "docility"
    },
    {
      "question": "having no employment  ",
      "answer": "idleness"
    },
    {
      "question": "in a figurative sense",
      "answer": "figuratively"
    },
    {
      "question": "someone whose occupation is cleaning  ",
      "answer": "cleaner"
    },
    {
      "question": "an artist of consummate skill",
      "answer": "maestro"
    },
    {
      "question": "large European marine food fish  ",
      "answer": "maigre"
    },
    {
      "question": "carrying boats and supplies overland  ",
      "answer": "portage"
    },
    {
      "question": "the act of someone appearing again",
      "answer": "reappearance"
    },
    {
      "question": "large scissors with strong blades  ",
      "answer": "shears"
    },
    {
      "question": "a person who abandons their duty (as on a military post)  ",
      "answer": "deserter"
    },
    {
      "question": "of e.g. advice  ",
      "answer": "unsound"
    },
    {
      "question": "coat, inlay, or surface with enamel  ",
      "answer": "enamel"
    },
    {
      "question": "constituting or like a nucleus",
      "answer": "nuclear"
    },
    {
      "question": "be a mystery or bewildering to",
      "answer": "perplex"
    },
    {
      "question": "prepare according to a formula  ",
      "answer": "formulate"
    },
    {
      "question": "characterized by active hostility",
      "answer": "opponent"
    },
    {
      "question": "the state of being potent",
      "answer": "potency"
    },
    {
      "question": "the trait of thinking carefully before acting  ",
      "answer": "thoughtfulness"
    },
    {
      "question": "of an electrical signal",
      "answer": "attenuated"
    },
    {
      "question": "someone who plays a drum  ",
      "answer": "drummer"
    },
    {
      "question": "an English coin worth half a penny  ",
      "answer": "halfpenny"
    },
    {
      "question": "unpleasantly cool and humid",
      "answer": "clammy"
    },
    {
      "question": "a spring-flowering shrub or small tree of the genus Crataegus  ",
      "answer": "hawthorn"
    },
    {
      "question": "shrubby tree with silky foliage and spikes of cylindrical yellow nectarous flowers  ",
      "answer": "honeysuckle"
    },
    {
      "question": "cause somebody to adapt or reform socially or politically  ",
      "answer": "reconstruct"
    },
    {
      "question": "a coarse cloth resembling sacking  ",
      "answer": "sackcloth"
    },
    {
      "question": "a shop that sells women's clothes and jewelry  ",
      "answer": "boutique"
    },
    {
      "question": "with respect to philosophy",
      "answer": "philosophically"
    },
    {
      "question": "tending to prevent or hinder  ",
      "answer": "preventive"
    },
    {
      "question": "in an apologetic manner",
      "answer": "apologetically"
    },
    {
      "question": "cannot be removed or erased",
      "answer": "indelible"
    },
    {
      "question": "inducing or influencing",
      "answer": "inductive"
    },
    {
      "question": "in a passive manner",
      "answer": "passively"
    },
    {
      "question": "lacking dignity  ",
      "answer": "undignified"
    },
    {
      "question": "a member of a legation  ",
      "answer": "legate"
    },
    {
      "question": "a hole in the ground made by excavating  ",
      "answer": "excavation"
    },
    {
      "question": "a synthetic silklike fabric  ",
      "answer": "rayon"
    },
    {
      "question": "hang on an execution instrument  ",
      "answer": "gibbet"
    },
    {
      "question": "remove the husks from",
      "answer": "husk"
    },
    {
      "question": "the state of being omnipotent",
      "answer": "omnipotence"
    },
    {
      "question": "reduced to submission",
      "answer": "subjugated"
    },
    {
      "question": "not well learned  ",
      "answer": "unlearned"
    },
    {
      "question": "of no value  ",
      "answer": "valueless"
    },
    {
      "question": "a white metallic element that burns with a brilliant light",
      "answer": "calcium"
    },
    {
      "question": "the right to take another's property if an obligation is not discharged  ",
      "answer": "lien"
    },
    {
      "question": "ineffectual chewing (as if without teeth)  ",
      "answer": "mumbling"
    },
    {
      "question": "a narrow fissure in rock  ",
      "answer": "rift"
    },
    {
      "question": "in an unaccountable manner",
      "answer": "unaccountably"
    },
    {
      "question": "a shortened version of a written work  ",
      "answer": "condensation"
    },
    {
      "question": "(geology) a rise of land to a higher elevation (as in the process of mountain building)  ",
      "answer": "upheaval"
    },
    {
      "question": "of or relating to the cerebrum or brain",
      "answer": "cerebral"
    },
    {
      "question": "decrease in value of an asset due to obsolescence or use  ",
      "answer": "depreciation"
    },
    {
      "question": "the group following and attending to some important person  ",
      "answer": "cortege"
    },
    {
      "question": "(of a knight's helmet) having a decorative plume  ",
      "answer": "crested"
    },
    {
      "question": "a grant paid by a government to an enterprise that benefits the public",
      "answer": "subsidy"
    },
    {
      "question": "traveling from place to place to work",
      "answer": "itinerant"
    },
    {
      "question": "lacking honor or integrity",
      "answer": "dishonorable"
    },
    {
      "question": "exceedingly or unbelievably great",
      "answer": "phenomenal"
    },
    {
      "question": "take the place of",
      "answer": "usurp"
    },
    {
      "question": "a loosely woven cord (in a candle or oil lamp) that draws fuel by capillary action up into the flame  ",
      "answer": "wick"
    },
    {
      "question": "the quality of being facile in speech and writing  ",
      "answer": "fluency"
    },
    {
      "question": "a card game played by one person  ",
      "answer": "solitaire"
    },
    {
      "question": "the state of being insubstantial or imaginary",
      "answer": "unreality"
    },
    {
      "question": "someone who manages a government agency or department  ",
      "answer": "administrator"
    },
    {
      "question": "someone who predicts the future by the positions of the planets and sun and Moon  ",
      "answer": "astrologer"
    },
    {
      "question": "a person who has suddenly risen to a higher economic status but has not gained social acceptance of others in that class  ",
      "answer": "upstart"
    },
    {
      "question": "the doctrine that government should not interfere in commercial affairs  ",
      "answer": "individualism"
    },
    {
      "question": "a room (often at the top of a tower) where bells are hung  ",
      "answer": "belfry"
    },
    {
      "question": "the 16th letter of the Greek alphabet  ",
      "answer": "pi"
    },
    {
      "question": "a string of beads used in counting prayers (especially by Catholics)  ",
      "answer": "rosary"
    },
    {
      "question": "a general officer ranking below a major general  ",
      "answer": "brigadier"
    },
    {
      "question": "make lively",
      "answer": "enliven"
    },
    {
      "question": "serious infection marked by intestinal inflammation and ulceration",
      "answer": "typhoid"
    },
    {
      "question": "provide commentary for a film, for example  ",
      "answer": "narrate"
    },
    {
      "question": "a prisoner who is held by one party to insure that another party will meet specified terms  ",
      "answer": "hostage"
    },
    {
      "question": "(astronomy) a heavenly body's highest celestial point above an observer's horizon  ",
      "answer": "culmination"
    },
    {
      "question": "remove all or part of one's clothes to show one's body",
      "answer": "uncover"
    },
    {
      "question": "any malignant growth or tumor caused by abnormal and uncontrolled cell division",
      "answer": "cancer"
    },
    {
      "question": "the act of prolonging something",
      "answer": "prolongation"
    },
    {
      "question": "beginning again  ",
      "answer": "resumption"
    },
    {
      "question": "like or characteristic of or befitting a sister",
      "answer": "sisterly"
    },
    {
      "question": "indistinctness of shape or character",
      "answer": "vagueness"
    },
    {
      "question": "voracious snakelike marine or freshwater fishes with smooth slimy usually scaleless skin and having a continuous vertical fin but no ventral fins  ",
      "answer": "eel"
    },
    {
      "question": "the quality of being universal",
      "answer": "universality"
    },
    {
      "question": "of or relating to dynamics  ",
      "answer": "dynamic"
    },
    {
      "question": "of or relating to senators",
      "answer": "senatorial"
    },
    {
      "question": "of a vivid red to reddish-orange color  ",
      "answer": "vermilion"
    },
    {
      "question": "of or relating to or characteristic of the planet Earth or its inhabitants",
      "answer": "planetary"
    },
    {
      "question": "to a restricted area of the body",
      "answer": "locally"
    },
    {
      "question": "freshwater carnivorous mammal having webbed and clawed feet and dark brown fur  ",
      "answer": "otter"
    },
    {
      "question": "impatient especially under restriction or delay",
      "answer": "restive"
    },
    {
      "question": "an anatomical structure used as a point of origin in locating other anatomical structures (as in surgery) or as point from which measurements can be taken  ",
      "answer": "landmark"
    },
    {
      "question": "a musical composition for two performers  ",
      "answer": "duet"
    },
    {
      "question": "characterized by iniquity",
      "answer": "iniquitous"
    },
    {
      "question": "preceding in time  ",
      "answer": "priority"
    },
    {
      "question": "lack of an adequate quantity or number",
      "answer": "insufficiency"
    },
    {
      "question": "sun-dried brick",
      "answer": "adobe"
    },
    {
      "question": "in an imperative and commanding manner  ",
      "answer": "imperatively"
    },
    {
      "question": "having the rank of or resembling or befitting a queen",
      "answer": "queenly"
    },
    {
      "question": "ride at a cantering pace",
      "answer": "canter"
    },
    {
      "question": "one who enters a competition  ",
      "answer": "entrant"
    },
    {
      "question": "a (usually long) dramatic speech intended to give the illusion of unspoken reflections  ",
      "answer": "soliloquy"
    },
    {
      "question": "a bottomless gulf or pit",
      "answer": "abyss"
    },
    {
      "question": "a drawing of the outlines of forms or objects  ",
      "answer": "delineation"
    },
    {
      "question": "disloyalty to the government or to established authority",
      "answer": "disaffection"
    },
    {
      "question": "a foreboding about what is about to happen  ",
      "answer": "presage"
    },
    {
      "question": "pleat or gather into a ruffle",
      "answer": "ruffle"
    },
    {
      "question": "(of an eye) reddened as a result of locally congested blood vessels",
      "answer": "bloodshot"
    },
    {
      "question": "of or pertaining to the outside surface of an object  ",
      "answer": "facial"
    },
    {
      "question": "a dissolute person",
      "answer": "libertine"
    },
    {
      "question": "pot for brewing tea",
      "answer": "teapot"
    },
    {
      "question": "free from undue bias or preconceived opinions",
      "answer": "unprejudiced"
    },
    {
      "question": "rum cut with water  ",
      "answer": "grog"
    },
    {
      "question": "characterized by often poignant difference or incongruity between what is expected and what actually is",
      "answer": "ironic"
    },
    {
      "question": "become or cause to become undone by separating the fibers or threads of",
      "answer": "unravel"
    },
    {
      "question": "a male servant (especially a footman)  ",
      "answer": "lackey"
    },
    {
      "question": "without luster or shine",
      "answer": "dully"
    },
    {
      "question": "detected by instinct or inference rather than by recognized perceptual cues",
      "answer": "sensed"
    },
    {
      "question": "the separation of grain or seeds from the husks and straw",
      "answer": "threshing"
    },
    {
      "question": "sever or remove by pinching or snipping",
      "answer": "nip"
    },
    {
      "question": "live longer than",
      "answer": "outlive"
    },
    {
      "question": "the quality or habit of adhering to an appointed time  ",
      "answer": "punctuality"
    },
    {
      "question": "a beckoning gesture  ",
      "answer": "beck"
    },
    {
      "question": "overcome by superior force  ",
      "answer": "overpower"
    },
    {
      "question": "the action of stupefying",
      "answer": "stupefaction"
    },
    {
      "question": "(used of color) artificially produced",
      "answer": "bleached"
    },
    {
      "question": "rebuke formally  ",
      "answer": "reprimand"
    },
    {
      "question": "(of weapons) not charged with ammunition",
      "answer": "unloaded"
    },
    {
      "question": "bite or chew on with the teeth",
      "answer": "gnaw"
    },
    {
      "question": "a receptacle into which an electric device can be inserted  ",
      "answer": "socket"
    },
    {
      "question": "marked by or capable of arousing controversy",
      "answer": "controversial"
    },
    {
      "question": "giving a Christian name at baptism  ",
      "answer": "christening"
    },
    {
      "question": "in a humorous manner",
      "answer": "humorously"
    },
    {
      "question": "someone trained in forestry  ",
      "answer": "forester"
    },
    {
      "question": "in an imperious manner",
      "answer": "imperiously"
    },
    {
      "question": "structure consisting of a row of evenly spaced columns  ",
      "answer": "colonnade"
    },
    {
      "question": "exhibiting lack of respect",
      "answer": "disrespectful"
    },
    {
      "question": "neckwear consisting of a long narrow piece of material worn (mostly by men) under a collar and tied in knot at the front",
      "answer": "necktie"
    },
    {
      "question": "place into enforced isolation, as for medical reasons",
      "answer": "quarantine"
    },
    {
      "question": "having a musical sound",
      "answer": "tuneful"
    },
    {
      "question": "incapable of being repudiated or transferred to another",
      "answer": "inalienable"
    },
    {
      "question": "a sailing vessel with two masts",
      "answer": "ketch"
    },
    {
      "question": "(usually plural) a destructive action",
      "answer": "ravage"
    },
    {
      "question": "a pastry cup with a filling of fruit or custard and no top crust  ",
      "answer": "tart"
    },
    {
      "question": "(of characters in literature or drama) tending to evoke antipathetic feelings",
      "answer": "unsympathetic"
    },
    {
      "question": "that toward which you are inclined to feel dislike",
      "answer": "disinclination"
    },
    {
      "question": "light from a lamp  ",
      "answer": "lamplight"
    },
    {
      "question": "catch with a lasso",
      "answer": "lasso"
    },
    {
      "question": "someone who is not a clergyman or a professional person  ",
      "answer": "layman"
    },
    {
      "question": "direct one's course or way",
      "answer": "wend"
    },
    {
      "question": "the mother of your father or mother  ",
      "answer": "grandma"
    },
    {
      "question": "remove by passing through a filter",
      "answer": "filter"
    },
    {
      "question": "grating that admits cooling air to car's radiator  ",
      "answer": "grille"
    },
    {
      "question": "characteristic of piracy",
      "answer": "piratical"
    },
    {
      "question": "the use of tricks to deceive someone (usually to extract money from them)  ",
      "answer": "trickery"
    },
    {
      "question": "seemingly contradictory but nonetheless possibly true",
      "answer": "paradoxical"
    },
    {
      "question": "any outer covering that can be shed or cast off (such as the cast-off skin of a snake)  ",
      "answer": "slough"
    },
    {
      "question": "servile flattery",
      "answer": "adulation"
    },
    {
      "question": "without speaking",
      "answer": "mutely"
    },
    {
      "question": "by right",
      "answer": "rightfully"
    },
    {
      "question": "a lack of belief in the existence of God or gods  ",
      "answer": "atheism"
    },
    {
      "question": "causing injury or blight",
      "answer": "blasting"
    },
    {
      "question": "issue an injunction  ",
      "answer": "enjoin"
    },
    {
      "question": "to a degree that exceeds the bounds or reason or moderation",
      "answer": "unreasonably"
    },
    {
      "question": "a pariah who is avoided by others  ",
      "answer": "leper"
    },
    {
      "question": "the action of alienating",
      "answer": "alienation"
    },
    {
      "question": "a person trained to compete in sports  ",
      "answer": "athlete"
    },
    {
      "question": "subject to limits or subjected to limits  ",
      "answer": "circumscribed"
    },
    {
      "question": "a ceremony to honor the memory of someone or something  ",
      "answer": "commemoration"
    },
    {
      "question": "a multivalent nonmetallic element of the nitrogen family that occurs commonly in inorganic phosphate rocks and as organic phosphates in all living cells",
      "answer": "phosphorus"
    },
    {
      "question": "characterized by resonance",
      "answer": "resonant"
    },
    {
      "question": "made easy or uncomplicated  ",
      "answer": "simplified"
    },
    {
      "question": "shake, quiver, or throb",
      "answer": "vibrate"
    },
    {
      "question": "a New Orleans district lying outside the original city limits",
      "answer": "faubourg"
    },
    {
      "question": "a negotiator who acts as a link between parties  ",
      "answer": "mediator"
    },
    {
      "question": "deprive of a necessity and cause suffering",
      "answer": "starve"
    },
    {
      "question": "the act of subdividing",
      "answer": "subdivision"
    },
    {
      "question": "in an amicable manner",
      "answer": "amicably"
    },
    {
      "question": "worn away or tattered along the edges",
      "answer": "frayed"
    },
    {
      "question": "a medicinal or magical or poisonous beverage  ",
      "answer": "potion"
    },
    {
      "question": "going from better to worse  ",
      "answer": "retrograde"
    },
    {
      "question": "with attention",
      "answer": "attentively"
    },
    {
      "question": "lessen the activity or force of",
      "answer": "depress"
    },
    {
      "question": "the act of augmenting  ",
      "answer": "augmentation"
    },
    {
      "question": "physically fit",
      "answer": "conditioned"
    },
    {
      "question": "a very poisonous metallic element that has three allotropic forms",
      "answer": "arsenic"
    },
    {
      "question": "treat with nitric acid, so as to change an organic compound into a nitrate",
      "answer": "nitrate"
    },
    {
      "question": "not deserved or earned",
      "answer": "undeserved"
    },
    {
      "question": "a programmer for whom computing is its own reward",
      "answer": "hacker"
    },
    {
      "question": "add embellishments and paintings to (medieval manuscripts)  ",
      "answer": "illuminate"
    },
    {
      "question": "make (one's senses) more acute",
      "answer": "sharpen"
    },
    {
      "question": "try to fix or mend",
      "answer": "tinker"
    },
    {
      "question": "careful examination and comparison to note points of disagreement  ",
      "answer": "collation"
    },
    {
      "question": "burdened with legal or financial obligations",
      "answer": "mortgaged"
    },
    {
      "question": "a disposition to be friendly and approachable (easy to talk to)  ",
      "answer": "affability"
    },
    {
      "question": "a citizen who has a legal right to vote  ",
      "answer": "voter"
    },
    {
      "question": "a covering of coarse fabric (usually of straw or hemp)  ",
      "answer": "matting"
    },
    {
      "question": "characterized by deliberate purpose and some degree of planning",
      "answer": "premeditated"
    },
    {
      "question": "browned over by exposure to heat",
      "answer": "toasted"
    },
    {
      "question": "the heating elements of a stove or range on which pots and pans are placed for cooking",
      "answer": "burner"
    },
    {
      "question": "issue an order  ",
      "answer": "ordain"
    },
    {
      "question": "eellike aquatic North American salamander with small forelimbs and no hind limbs",
      "answer": "siren"
    },
    {
      "question": "belonging to this earth or world",
      "answer": "mundane"
    },
    {
      "question": "lacking in discipline or control",
      "answer": "undisciplined"
    },
    {
      "question": "corresponding in size or degree or extent",
      "answer": "commensurate"
    },
    {
      "question": "a political advocate of socialism  ",
      "answer": "socialist"
    },
    {
      "question": "(of reputation) free from blemishes",
      "answer": "stainless"
    },
    {
      "question": "fresh",
      "answer": "caller"
    },
    {
      "question": "the study of the sources and development of words  ",
      "answer": "etymology"
    },
    {
      "question": "plaything consisting of a small model of a house that children can play inside of  ",
      "answer": "playhouse"
    },
    {
      "question": "of or relating to or typical of a revenant",
      "answer": "revenant"
    },
    {
      "question": "any of various organs that synthesize substances needed by the body and release it through ducts or directly into the bloodstream  ",
      "answer": "gland"
    },
    {
      "question": "in an incredulous manner",
      "answer": "incredulously"
    },
    {
      "question": "able to move freely in all directions",
      "answer": "versatile"
    },
    {
      "question": "of hair color",
      "answer": "flaxen"
    },
    {
      "question": "a framework with hooks used for stretching and drying cloth  ",
      "answer": "tenter"
    },
    {
      "question": "admitting of no doubt or misunderstanding",
      "answer": "unequivocal"
    },
    {
      "question": "freed from any question of guilt",
      "answer": "absolved"
    },
    {
      "question": "the condition of being unable to perform as a consequence of physical or mental unfitness",
      "answer": "disability"
    },
    {
      "question": "the part of the alimentary canal between the stomach and the anus  ",
      "answer": "intestine"
    },
    {
      "question": "a period of dullness or boredom (especially in a work of literature or performing art)  ",
      "answer": "longueur"
    },
    {
      "question": "sufficiently fat so as to have a pleasing fullness of figure",
      "answer": "chubby"
    },
    {
      "question": "enclosed in a protective covering",
      "answer": "sheathed"
    },
    {
      "question": " allowing light to pass through diffusely",
      "answer": "translucent"
    },
    {
      "question": "become glad or happy  ",
      "answer": "gladden"
    },
    {
      "question": "young of any of various canines such as a dog or wolf  ",
      "answer": "pup"
    },
    {
      "question": "extend in scope or range or area",
      "answer": "widen"
    },
    {
      "question": "a fabric with a nap that is longer and softer than velvet  ",
      "answer": "plush"
    },
    {
      "question": "a person who receives support and protection from an influential patron who furthers the protege's career  ",
      "answer": "protege"
    },
    {
      "question": "arranged in a stack  ",
      "answer": "stacked"
    },
    {
      "question": "in an unceremonious manner",
      "answer": "unceremoniously"
    },
    {
      "question": "lodge in barracks  ",
      "answer": "barrack"
    },
    {
      "question": "flesh of a pheasant",
      "answer": "pheasant"
    },
    {
      "question": "the quality of not putting yourself first but being willing to give your time or money or effort etc. for others",
      "answer": "unselfishness"
    },
    {
      "question": "a person who charms others (usually by personal attractiveness)  ",
      "answer": "charmer"
    },
    {
      "question": "a biologist specializing in the study of plants  ",
      "answer": "botanist"
    },
    {
      "question": "the trait of being circumspect and prudent  ",
      "answer": "circumspection"
    },
    {
      "question": "embroider with gold or silver thread  ",
      "answer": "purl"
    },
    {
      "question": "having no tracks",
      "answer": "trackless"
    },
    {
      "question": "not injured physically or mentally  ",
      "answer": "uninjured"
    },
    {
      "question": "decrease in phase",
      "answer": "wane"
    },
    {
      "question": "any succulent plant of the family Cactaceae native chiefly to arid regions of the New World and usually having spines  ",
      "answer": "cactus"
    },
    {
      "question": "a flowing together  ",
      "answer": "confluence"
    },
    {
      "question": "suggesting connivance",
      "answer": "cozy"
    },
    {
      "question": "the rise of something",
      "answer": "uplifting"
    },
    {
      "question": "any of various Chinese boats with a high poop and lugsails  ",
      "answer": "junk"
    },
    {
      "question": "a diplomat who is fully authorized to represent his or her government  ",
      "answer": "plenipotentiary"
    },
    {
      "question": "confined or restricted with or as if with a rope or chain  ",
      "answer": "tethered"
    },
    {
      "question": "used of the degree of something undesirable e.g. pain or weather  ",
      "answer": "badness"
    },
    {
      "question": "make invalid for use",
      "answer": "cancel"
    },
    {
      "question": "device used for an infant to suck or bite on  ",
      "answer": "comforter"
    },
    {
      "question": "visit again",
      "answer": "revisit"
    },
    {
      "question": "make slack as by lessening tension or firmness  ",
      "answer": "slacken"
    },
    {
      "question": "tending to vanish like vapor",
      "answer": "evanescent"
    },
    {
      "question": "in a gingerly manner",
      "answer": "gingerly"
    },
    {
      "question": "a flock of snipe  ",
      "answer": "wisp"
    },
    {
      "question": "that infects or taints  ",
      "answer": "corrupting"
    },
    {
      "question": "belonging to or characteristic of a sect",
      "answer": "sectarian"
    },
    {
      "question": "intellectually appealing",
      "answer": "sophisticated"
    },
    {
      "question": "the act of obstructing or deflecting someone's movements  ",
      "answer": "blocking"
    },
    {
      "question": "incapable of absorbing or mixing with",
      "answer": "repellent"
    },
    {
      "question": "check, track, or observe by means of a receiver  ",
      "answer": "monitor"
    },
    {
      "question": "a person who is a member of an ethnic group  ",
      "answer": "ethnic"
    },
    {
      "question": "having more than one spouse at a time  ",
      "answer": "polygamy"
    },
    {
      "question": "act as a critic",
      "answer": "criticize"
    },
    {
      "question": "in a lawfully recognized manner",
      "answer": "legitimately"
    },
    {
      "question": "any of various minerals consisting of hydrous silicates of aluminum or potassium etc. that crystallize in forms that allow perfect cleavage into very thin leaves",
      "answer": "mica"
    },
    {
      "question": "the property of being perpetual (seemingly ceaseless)  ",
      "answer": "perpetuity"
    },
    {
      "question": "provide with or construct with studs",
      "answer": "stud"
    },
    {
      "question": "utter or make a noise, as when swallowing too quickly",
      "answer": "gulp"
    },
    {
      "question": "furnished with inhabitants",
      "answer": "populated"
    },
    {
      "question": "make withdrawn or isolated or emotionally dissociated",
      "answer": "alienate"
    },
    {
      "question": "a child: son or daughter  ",
      "answer": "bairn"
    },
    {
      "question": "any of numerous composite plants having flower heads with well-developed ray flowers usually arranged in a single whorl  ",
      "answer": "daisy"
    },
    {
      "question": "(law) the residence where you have your permanent home or principal establishment and to where, whenever you are absent, you intend to return",
      "answer": "domicile"
    },
    {
      "question": "heard through another rather than directly",
      "answer": "hearsay"
    },
    {
      "question": "able to be passed or traversed or crossed",
      "answer": "passable"
    },
    {
      "question": "excrete or discharge from the body  ",
      "answer": "evacuate"
    },
    {
      "question": "having or resembling a finger or fingers",
      "answer": "fingered"
    },
    {
      "question": "decoration consisting of an open pattern of interlacing ribs  ",
      "answer": "tracery"
    },
    {
      "question": "the time you go to bed  ",
      "answer": "bedtime"
    },
    {
      "question": "a British peer who ranks below an earl and above a baron  ",
      "answer": "viscount"
    },
    {
      "question": "run or flow slowly, as in drops or in an unsteady stream",
      "answer": "trickle"
    },
    {
      "question": "hand-operated character printer for printing written messages one character at a time  ",
      "answer": "typewriter"
    },
    {
      "question": "a writer who reports and analyzes events of the day  ",
      "answer": "commentator"
    },
    {
      "question": "remove crumbs from",
      "answer": "crumb"
    },
    {
      "question": "off the subject",
      "answer": "afield"
    },
    {
      "question": "heard or perceptible by the ear",
      "answer": "audible"
    },
    {
      "question": "(law) tacit approval of someone's wrongdoing  ",
      "answer": "connivance"
    },
    {
      "question": "a person who has been freed from slavery  ",
      "answer": "freedman"
    },
    {
      "question": "the action of accomplishing something  ",
      "answer": "accomplishment"
    },
    {
      "question": "characterized by or full of force or strength (often but not necessarily physical)",
      "answer": "forceful"
    },
    {
      "question": "the combination of ideas into a complex whole  ",
      "answer": "synthesis"
    },
    {
      "question": "become similar in sound",
      "answer": "assimilate"
    },
    {
      "question": "repair by sewing",
      "answer": "darn"
    },
    {
      "question": "a highway  ",
      "answer": "highroad"
    },
    {
      "question": "habitually moving from place to place especially in search of seasonal work",
      "answer": "migrant"
    },
    {
      "question": "feeling or expressing pain or sorrow for sins or offenses  ",
      "answer": "contrite"
    },
    {
      "question": "a soft pebble-grained leather made from goatskin",
      "answer": "morocco"
    },
    {
      "question": "incapable of being morally corrupted",
      "answer": "incorruptible"
    },
    {
      "question": "the immature free-living form of most invertebrates and amphibians and fish which at hatching from the egg is fundamentally unlike its parent and must metamorphose  ",
      "answer": "larva"
    },
    {
      "question": "an inadequate payment",
      "answer": "pittance"
    },
    {
      "question": "a short excursion (a walk or ride) in the open air",
      "answer": "airing"
    },
    {
      "question": "not made opaque or cloudy by sediment",
      "answer": "unclouded"
    },
    {
      "question": "unpleasant to look at",
      "answer": "unsightly"
    },
    {
      "question": "a part that is joined to something larger  ",
      "answer": "appendage"
    },
    {
      "question": "cut a bevel on",
      "answer": "bevel"
    },
    {
      "question": "a sedan that has no roof over the driver's seat  ",
      "answer": "brougham"
    },
    {
      "question": "diaphragm consisting of thin overlapping plates that can be adjusted to change the diameter of a central opening  ",
      "answer": "iris"
    },
    {
      "question": "in a pensive manner",
      "answer": "pensively"
    },
    {
      "question": "not diminished or moderated in intensity or severity",
      "answer": "unmitigated"
    },
    {
      "question": "characteristic of an orator or oratory",
      "answer": "oratorical"
    },
    {
      "question": "blow gently",
      "answer": "waft"
    },
    {
      "question": "(of the moon) pertaining to the period during which the visible surface of the moon increases",
      "answer": "waxing"
    },
    {
      "question": "unusually short",
      "answer": "snub"
    },
    {
      "question": "narrowly restricted in outlook or scope",
      "answer": "insular"
    },
    {
      "question": "an edge tool for cutting grass or crops",
      "answer": "sickle"
    },
    {
      "question": "not dense",
      "answer": "sparse"
    },
    {
      "question": "people living in a town or city having local self-government  ",
      "answer": "municipality"
    },
    {
      "question": "work (such as sewing or embroidery) that is done with a needle  ",
      "answer": "needlework"
    },
    {
      "question": "a word that modifies something other than a noun  ",
      "answer": "adverb"
    },
    {
      "question": "capable of being attributed",
      "answer": "attributable"
    },
    {
      "question": "decorate with, or as if with, gold leaf or liquid gold  ",
      "answer": "gild"
    },
    {
      "question": "a set of clothing (with accessories)",
      "answer": "outfit"
    },
    {
      "question": "an event that departs from expectations  ",
      "answer": "discrepancy"
    },
    {
      "question": "a cord-like tissue connecting two larger parts of an anatomical structure  ",
      "answer": "isthmus"
    },
    {
      "question": "a device (usually metal and ornamental) attached by a hinge to a door  ",
      "answer": "knocker"
    },
    {
      "question": "developing in intricate and painstaking detail  ",
      "answer": "elaboration"
    },
    {
      "question": "pasta in the form of slender tubes  ",
      "answer": "macaroni"
    },
    {
      "question": "lacking or showing lack of judgment or discretion",
      "answer": "injudicious"
    },
    {
      "question": "lively attentiveness  ",
      "answer": "alertness"
    },
    {
      "question": "in an insolent manner",
      "answer": "insolently"
    },
    {
      "question": "righteousness as a consequence of being honorable and honest  ",
      "answer": "uprightness"
    },
    {
      "question": "most powerful or important or influential",
      "answer": "ascendant"
    },
    {
      "question": "full of pores or vessels or holes  ",
      "answer": "porous"
    },
    {
      "question": "based on an incorrect or misleading notion or information",
      "answer": "fallacious"
    },
    {
      "question": "illegality as a consequence of unlawful acts",
      "answer": "lawlessness"
    },
    {
      "question": "a song of devotion or loyalty (as to a nation or school)  ",
      "answer": "anthem"
    },
    {
      "question": "without pity",
      "answer": "mercilessly"
    },
    {
      "question": "a general disposition to look on the dark side and to expect the worst in all things  ",
      "answer": "pessimism"
    },
    {
      "question": "place out of sight",
      "answer": "secrete"
    },
    {
      "question": "ring as in announcing death  ",
      "answer": "knell"
    },
    {
      "question": "in a surreptitious manner",
      "answer": "surreptitiously"
    },
    {
      "question": "occurring in the same period of time",
      "answer": "contemporaneous"
    },
    {
      "question": "abusing vocally",
      "answer": "derisive"
    },
    {
      "question": "a loss (or serious disruption) of organization in some system",
      "answer": "disintegration"
    },
    {
      "question": "wild or domesticated South American cud-chewing animal related to camels but smaller and lacking a hump  ",
      "answer": "llama"
    },
    {
      "question": "make moist",
      "answer": "moisten"
    },
    {
      "question": "express the same message in different words  ",
      "answer": "paraphrase"
    },
    {
      "question": "be specific about",
      "answer": "specify"
    },
    {
      "question": "turned or stirred by plowing or harrowing or hoeing",
      "answer": "tilled"
    },
    {
      "question": "a method of representing the sounds of a language by written or printed symbols  ",
      "answer": "orthography"
    },
    {
      "question": "edible young shoots of the asparagus plant  ",
      "answer": "asparagus"
    },
    {
      "question": "a substance believed to cure all ills  ",
      "answer": "elixir"
    },
    {
      "question": "a person who is feeling grief (as grieving over someone who has died)  ",
      "answer": "mourner"
    },
    {
      "question": "just below the level of consciousness  ",
      "answer": "subconscious"
    },
    {
      "question": "a pseudoscience claiming divination by the positions of the planets and sun and moon  ",
      "answer": "astrology"
    },
    {
      "question": "consider or ponder something carefully",
      "answer": "bethink"
    },
    {
      "question": "unrestrained by convention or morality",
      "answer": "debauched"
    },
    {
      "question": "the time of life when sex glands become functional  ",
      "answer": "puberty"
    },
    {
      "question": "the state (usually of a woman) of having no children or being unable to have children  ",
      "answer": "barrenness"
    },
    {
      "question": "the distance around a person's body  ",
      "answer": "girth"
    },
    {
      "question": "someone skilled in the transcription of speech (especially dictation)  ",
      "answer": "stenographer"
    },
    {
      "question": "having existence or being or actuality",
      "answer": "existent"
    },
    {
      "question": "(physics) the tendency of a body to maintain its state of rest or uniform motion unless acted upon by an external force  ",
      "answer": "inertia"
    },
    {
      "question": "the hole where a key is inserted  ",
      "answer": "keyhole"
    },
    {
      "question": "a record in which commercial accounts are recorded",
      "answer": "ledger"
    },
    {
      "question": "a radial arrangement of nerve fibers connecting different parts of the brain  ",
      "answer": "radiation"
    },
    {
      "question": "of a light brownish color  ",
      "answer": "sorrel"
    },
    {
      "question": "coverings that are used on a bed  ",
      "answer": "bedclothes"
    },
    {
      "question": "shopping at a market",
      "answer": "marketing"
    },
    {
      "question": "supplying or being a final or conclusive settlement",
      "answer": "definitive"
    },
    {
      "question": "a high-ranking university administrator  ",
      "answer": "provost"
    },
    {
      "question": "leaves can be used as seasoning for almost any meat and stews and stuffings and vegetables  ",
      "answer": "thyme"
    },
    {
      "question": "full of trouble",
      "answer": "troublous"
    },
    {
      "question": "compromise oneself for money or other gains",
      "answer": "whore"
    },
    {
      "question": "calling up a spirit or devil  ",
      "answer": "conjuring"
    },
    {
      "question": "of or relating to baptism",
      "answer": "baptismal"
    },
    {
      "question": "a finely woven white linen  ",
      "answer": "cambric"
    },
    {
      "question": "a wormlike and often brightly colored and hairy or spiny larva of a butterfly or moth  ",
      "answer": "caterpillar"
    },
    {
      "question": "an unmarried status  ",
      "answer": "celibacy"
    },
    {
      "question": "produced by crossbreeding  ",
      "answer": "hybrid"
    },
    {
      "question": "the change in direction of a propagating wave (light or sound) when passing from one medium to another  ",
      "answer": "refraction"
    },
    {
      "question": "in a searching manner",
      "answer": "searchingly"
    },
    {
      "question": "the act of arranging in grades  ",
      "answer": "gradation"
    },
    {
      "question": "(in an election with more than 2 options) the number of votes for the candidate or party receiving the greatest number (but less that half of the votes)  ",
      "answer": "plurality"
    },
    {
      "question": "the quality of happening with headlong haste or without warning  ",
      "answer": "abruptness"
    },
    {
      "question": "a tall slender dog of an ancient breed noted for swiftness and keen sight",
      "answer": "greyhound"
    },
    {
      "question": "pass beyond (limits or boundaries)  ",
      "answer": "transgress"
    },
    {
      "question": "covered with growing timber",
      "answer": "timbered"
    },
    {
      "question": "women as distinguished from men  ",
      "answer": "womankind"
    },
    {
      "question": "a state of depression",
      "answer": "blues"
    },
    {
      "question": "covered as if with a cap or crown especially of a specified kind",
      "answer": "capped"
    },
    {
      "question": "the domain controlled by an earl or count or countess  ",
      "answer": "earldom"
    },
    {
      "question": "in a place across an ocean  ",
      "answer": "overseas"
    },
    {
      "question": "apply a salve to, usually for the purpose of healing  ",
      "answer": "salve"
    },
    {
      "question": "lacking accompaniment or a guard or escort",
      "answer": "unattended"
    },
    {
      "question": "including by incorporating  ",
      "answer": "incorporation"
    },
    {
      "question": "a humorist who uses ridicule and irony and sarcasm  ",
      "answer": "satirist"
    },
    {
      "question": "make a loud noise, as of animal",
      "answer": "bellow"
    },
    {
      "question": "shaping metal by heating and hammering  ",
      "answer": "forging"
    },
    {
      "question": "(of hair) colored a moderate reddish-brown",
      "answer": "auburn"
    },
    {
      "question": "an artificial reservoir for storing liquids",
      "answer": "cistern"
    },
    {
      "question": "read with difficulty",
      "answer": "decipher"
    },
    {
      "question": "in a sedulous manner",
      "answer": "sedulously"
    },
    {
      "question": "(ancient Rome) the leader of 100 soldiers  ",
      "answer": "centurion"
    },
    {
      "question": "make amends for",
      "answer": "expiate"
    },
    {
      "question": "of or relating to a belief in sacerdotalism",
      "answer": "sacerdotal"
    },
    {
      "question": "one who reveals confidential information in return for money  ",
      "answer": "informer"
    },
    {
      "question": "of a firearm",
      "answer": "rifled"
    },
    {
      "question": "having a hard nonresonant metallic sound",
      "answer": "clanking"
    },
    {
      "question": "force to leave (an office)  ",
      "answer": "depose"
    },
    {
      "question": "fill something that had previously been emptied",
      "answer": "replenish"
    },
    {
      "question": "(physiology) the effect of a stimulus (on nerves or organs etc.)  ",
      "answer": "stimulation"
    },
    {
      "question": "any living or extinct member of the family Hominidae characterized by superior intelligence, articulate speech, and erect carriage  ",
      "answer": "homo"
    },
    {
      "question": "liberality in bestowing gifts",
      "answer": "munificence"
    },
    {
      "question": "a short high-pitched noise",
      "answer": "squeak"
    },
    {
      "question": "a professional clown employed to entertain a king or nobleman in the Middle Ages  ",
      "answer": "jester"
    },
    {
      "question": "morally corrupt or evil",
      "answer": "putrid"
    },
    {
      "question": "give taste to  ",
      "answer": "savor"
    },
    {
      "question": "avoiding or escaping from difficulty or danger especially enemy fire",
      "answer": "evasive"
    },
    {
      "question": "having no or imperfectly developed or nonfunctional sex organs  ",
      "answer": "neuter"
    },
    {
      "question": "of or characteristic of a parvenu  ",
      "answer": "parvenu"
    },
    {
      "question": "the act of intersecting (as joining by causing your path to intersect your target's path)  ",
      "answer": "intersection"
    },
    {
      "question": "(law) a gift of personal property by will  ",
      "answer": "bequest"
    },
    {
      "question": "not continuing to grow indefinitely at the apex",
      "answer": "determinate"
    },
    {
      "question": "the act of bringing near or bringing together especially the cut edges of tissue  ",
      "answer": "approximation"
    },
    {
      "question": "disregarded",
      "answer": "ignored"
    },
    {
      "question": "characterized by ardent emotion or intensity or brilliance",
      "answer": "incandescent"
    },
    {
      "question": "someone who keeps safe from harm or danger  ",
      "answer": "preserver"
    },
    {
      "question": "extremely ominous",
      "answer": "thunderous"
    },
    {
      "question": "lacking in insight or discernment",
      "answer": "obtuse"
    },
    {
      "question": "layers of ice cream and syrup and whipped cream  ",
      "answer": "parfait"
    },
    {
      "question": "bind with something round or circular  ",
      "answer": "gird"
    },
    {
      "question": "grouping by class or kind or size  ",
      "answer": "sorting"
    },
    {
      "question": "(in formal usage, especially legal usage) for that or for it",
      "answer": "therefor"
    },
    {
      "question": "without beauty or charm  ",
      "answer": "unlovely"
    },
    {
      "question": "capable of igniting and burning  ",
      "answer": "combustible"
    },
    {
      "question": "tennis played with two players on each side  ",
      "answer": "doubles"
    },
    {
      "question": "the act of subjecting to strong attack  ",
      "answer": "battering"
    },
    {
      "question": "all the animal life in a particular region or period",
      "answer": "fauna"
    },
    {
      "question": "a political or theological orientation advocating the preservation of the best in society and opposing radical changes  ",
      "answer": "conservatism"
    },
    {
      "question": "in a dreadful manner",
      "answer": "dismally"
    },
    {
      "question": "a supply of food especially for a household  ",
      "answer": "larder"
    },
    {
      "question": "act of putting off to a future time  ",
      "answer": "postponement"
    },
    {
      "question": "fine particles of wood made by sawing wood  ",
      "answer": "sawdust"
    },
    {
      "question": "become free",
      "answer": "disengage"
    },
    {
      "question": "something intended to misrepresent the true nature of an activity",
      "answer": "subterfuge"
    },
    {
      "question": "make an unsuccessful effort to vomit",
      "answer": "gag"
    },
    {
      "question": "someone who obtains or acquires",
      "answer": "procurer"
    },
    {
      "question": "compulsory military service  ",
      "answer": "conscription"
    },
    {
      "question": "not in keeping with what is correct or proper",
      "answer": "inappropriate"
    },
    {
      "question": "the manner in which something is expressed in words",
      "answer": "wording"
    },
    {
      "question": "applaud with shouts of `bravo' or `brava'  ",
      "answer": "bravo"
    },
    {
      "question": "made of cloth spun or woven in the home",
      "answer": "homespun"
    },
    {
      "question": "consider again (a bill) that had been voted upon before, with a view to altering it  ",
      "answer": "reconsider"
    },
    {
      "question": "easily managed (controlled or taught or molded)",
      "answer": "tractable"
    },
    {
      "question": "a female lion  ",
      "answer": "lioness"
    },
    {
      "question": "reformed spiritually or morally",
      "answer": "regenerate"
    },
    {
      "question": "the cultivation of soil for raising crops  ",
      "answer": "tillage"
    },
    {
      "question": "make watertight",
      "answer": "waterproof"
    },
    {
      "question": "a judgment of not guilty  ",
      "answer": "acquittal"
    },
    {
      "question": "a bowl-shaped drinking vessel",
      "answer": "chalice"
    },
    {
      "question": "a council convened to discuss ecclesiastical business  ",
      "answer": "synod"
    },
    {
      "question": "covering or applying simultaneously to a number of similar items or elements or groups",
      "answer": "umbrella"
    },
    {
      "question": "(astronomy) the luminous cloud of particles surrounding the frozen nucleus of a comet",
      "answer": "coma"
    },
    {
      "question": "money received from the state  ",
      "answer": "dole"
    },
    {
      "question": "an incorrect conception  ",
      "answer": "misconception"
    },
    {
      "question": "cover with a material such as stone or concrete to make suitable for vehicle traffic",
      "answer": "pave"
    },
    {
      "question": "briefly shut the eyes",
      "answer": "blink"
    },
    {
      "question": "someone who is critical of the motives of others  ",
      "answer": "cynic"
    },
    {
      "question": "immeasurably small  ",
      "answer": "atomic"
    },
    {
      "question": "of or relating to or characteristic of humanitarianism",
      "answer": "humanitarian"
    },
    {
      "question": "anything that is owed to someone else  ",
      "answer": "liabilities"
    },
    {
      "question": "evil or harmful in nature or influence",
      "answer": "malign"
    },
    {
      "question": "in a royal manner",
      "answer": "royally"
    },
    {
      "question": "not damaged or diminished in any respect",
      "answer": "unimpaired"
    },
    {
      "question": "the act of joining things in such a way that motion is possible  ",
      "answer": "articulation"
    },
    {
      "question": "occupied with or fond of the pleasures of good company",
      "answer": "convivial"
    },
    {
      "question": "give off, send forth, or discharge",
      "answer": "emit"
    },
    {
      "question": "in a fluent manner",
      "answer": "fluently"
    },
    {
      "question": "having an abundant supply of money or possessions of value",
      "answer": "affluent"
    },
    {
      "question": "deprived of courage and strength",
      "answer": "unnerved"
    },
    {
      "question": "in the theories of Jean Piaget: the application of a general schema to a particular instance  ",
      "answer": "assimilation"
    },
    {
      "question": "branched lighting fixture",
      "answer": "chandelier"
    },
    {
      "question": "a confidential or secret meeting  ",
      "answer": "conclave"
    },
    {
      "question": "excessive spending  ",
      "answer": "extravagance"
    },
    {
      "question": "characterized or caused by inflammation",
      "answer": "inflammatory"
    },
    {
      "question": "a gambler who loses a bet  ",
      "answer": "loser"
    },
    {
      "question": "settle as sediment  ",
      "answer": "sediment"
    },
    {
      "question": "the syllable naming the sixth (submediant) note of a major or minor scale in solmization  ",
      "answer": "la"
    },
    {
      "question": "a person qualified to practice dentistry  ",
      "answer": "dentist"
    },
    {
      "question": "morally wholesome or acceptable",
      "answer": "savory"
    },
    {
      "question": "run away in a stampede  ",
      "answer": "stampede"
    },
    {
      "question": "an act intending or showing kindness and good will  ",
      "answer": "benevolence"
    },
    {
      "question": "related or limited to a particular region",
      "answer": "regional"
    },
    {
      "question": "one who practices magic or sorcery  ",
      "answer": "sorcerer"
    },
    {
      "question": "continuing at full strength or intensity",
      "answer": "unabated"
    },
    {
      "question": "of colors that are bright and striking  ",
      "answer": "vibrant"
    },
    {
      "question": "concern with things of the spirit  ",
      "answer": "spirituality"
    },
    {
      "question": "in a proud and domineering manner",
      "answer": "disdainfully"
    },
    {
      "question": "either of two saclike respiratory organs in the chest of vertebrates",
      "answer": "lung"
    },
    {
      "question": "a feeling of spontaneous good spirits",
      "answer": "cheerfulness"
    },
    {
      "question": "any wind that changes direction with the seasons  ",
      "answer": "monsoon"
    },
    {
      "question": "the cheapest accommodations on a passenger ship  ",
      "answer": "steerage"
    },
    {
      "question": "extremely hot",
      "answer": "torrid"
    },
    {
      "question": "an artifact (or system of artifacts) that is instrumental in accomplishing some end  ",
      "answer": "instrumentality"
    },
    {
      "question": "an infective disease caused by sporozoan parasites that are transmitted through the bite of an infected Anopheles mosquito",
      "answer": "malaria"
    },
    {
      "question": "a puzzle where you decode a message consisting of pictures representing syllables and words  ",
      "answer": "rebus"
    },
    {
      "question": "(Middle Ages) a person who is bound to the land and owned by the feudal lord  ",
      "answer": "serf"
    },
    {
      "question": "active support of an idea or cause etc.",
      "answer": "advocacy"
    },
    {
      "question": "the psychological result of perception and learning and reasoning  ",
      "answer": "cognition"
    },
    {
      "question": "having both internal structure and external form of a crystal",
      "answer": "crystallized"
    },
    {
      "question": "(of farmland) broken and turned over with a plow",
      "answer": "plowed"
    },
    {
      "question": "the quality or attribute of being unstable and irresolute  ",
      "answer": "instability"
    },
    {
      "question": "liable to or deserving punishment",
      "answer": "punishable"
    },
    {
      "question": "composed of one legislative body  ",
      "answer": "unicameral"
    },
    {
      "question": "emit a cloud of fine particles",
      "answer": "fume"
    },
    {
      "question": "produce (energy)",
      "answer": "generate"
    },
    {
      "question": "the commercial activity of buying and bringing in goods from a foreign country  ",
      "answer": "importing"
    },
    {
      "question": "the act of making something wet  ",
      "answer": "wetting"
    },
    {
      "question": "related to or written for or performed by a chorus or choir",
      "answer": "choral"
    },
    {
      "question": "wale at the top of the side of boat",
      "answer": "gunwale"
    },
    {
      "question": "any of numerous extinct elephants widely distributed in the Pleistocene",
      "answer": "mammoth"
    },
    {
      "question": "inclined to believe or confide readily",
      "answer": "trustful"
    },
    {
      "question": "a (usually long) dramatic speech by a single actor  ",
      "answer": "monologue"
    },
    {
      "question": "not lessened or diminished",
      "answer": "undiminished"
    },
    {
      "question": "common black European thrush  ",
      "answer": "blackbird"
    },
    {
      "question": "tastelessness by virtue of being cheap and vulgar  ",
      "answer": "cheapness"
    },
    {
      "question": "an act of winning the love or sexual favor of someone  ",
      "answer": "seduction"
    },
    {
      "question": "take the place or move into the position of",
      "answer": "supplant"
    },
    {
      "question": "feel a sudden sharp, local pain  ",
      "answer": "twinge"
    },
    {
      "question": "give off smoke, fumes, warm vapour, steam, etc.",
      "answer": "reek"
    },
    {
      "question": "a small channel (as one formed by soil erosion)  ",
      "answer": "rill"
    },
    {
      "question": "showing a cheerful willingness to do favors for others",
      "answer": "complaisant"
    },
    {
      "question": "planted so as to give an effect of wild growth",
      "answer": "naturalized"
    },
    {
      "question": "the scientific study of food and drink (especially in humans)  ",
      "answer": "nutrition"
    },
    {
      "question": "with efficiency",
      "answer": "efficiently"
    },
    {
      "question": "inaccessibly located or situated",
      "answer": "unapproachable"
    },
    {
      "question": "afflicted with or marked by anxious uneasiness or trouble or grief",
      "answer": "disquieted"
    },
    {
      "question": "the act of abating",
      "answer": "abatement"
    },
    {
      "question": "bend one's back forward from the waist on down",
      "answer": "crouch"
    },
    {
      "question": "the felonious act of extorting money (as by threats of violence)  ",
      "answer": "extortion"
    },
    {
      "question": "a single tone repeated with different words or different rhythms (especially in rendering liturgical texts)  ",
      "answer": "monotone"
    },
    {
      "question": "young tree  ",
      "answer": "sapling"
    },
    {
      "question": "the act of distributing by allotting or apportioning",
      "answer": "allotment"
    },
    {
      "question": "an insubordinate act  ",
      "answer": "insubordination"
    },
    {
      "question": "an enduring or necessary ethical or religious or aesthetic truth  ",
      "answer": "verity"
    },
    {
      "question": "venomous Old World snakes characterized by hollow venom-conducting fangs in the upper jaw  ",
      "answer": "viper"
    },
    {
      "question": "characteristic of informal spoken language or conversation",
      "answer": "colloquial"
    },
    {
      "question": "of or relating to the scientific study of language",
      "answer": "linguistic"
    },
    {
      "question": "adroitness and cleverness in reply  ",
      "answer": "repartee"
    },
    {
      "question": "develop a fine network of cracks",
      "answer": "craze"
    },
    {
      "question": "any animals kept for use or profit  ",
      "answer": "livestock"
    },
    {
      "question": "in a tremulous manner",
      "answer": "tremulously"
    },
    {
      "question": "a farewell remark",
      "answer": "adieu"
    },
    {
      "question": "sexual allure  ",
      "answer": "attractiveness"
    },
    {
      "question": "a journey to a sacred place  ",
      "answer": "pilgrimage"
    },
    {
      "question": "sell articles, television programs, or photos to several publications or independent broadcasting stations  ",
      "answer": "syndicate"
    },
    {
      "question": "relating to or supported by or located in a parish",
      "answer": "parochial"
    },
    {
      "question": "easily impressed or influenced",
      "answer": "impressionable"
    },
    {
      "question": "someone who asks a question  ",
      "answer": "inquirer"
    },
    {
      "question": "able to absorb liquid (not repellent)",
      "answer": "receptive"
    },
    {
      "question": "in a useful manner",
      "answer": "usefully"
    },
    {
      "question": "talk in a monotonous voice  ",
      "answer": "drone"
    },
    {
      "question": "make a slave of",
      "answer": "enslave"
    },
    {
      "question": "excellence of manners or social conduct  ",
      "answer": "graciousness"
    },
    {
      "question": "sticking fast  ",
      "answer": "adherent"
    },
    {
      "question": "characterized by or divided into or containing cells or compartments (the smallest organizational or structural unit of an organism or organization)",
      "answer": "cellular"
    },
    {
      "question": "expecting the best in this best of all possible worlds",
      "answer": "optimistic"
    },
    {
      "question": "making worse  ",
      "answer": "aggravating"
    },
    {
      "question": "made or become less intense",
      "answer": "deadened"
    },
    {
      "question": "a person who pursues some plan or goal",
      "answer": "pursuer"
    },
    {
      "question": "not conventional or conformist",
      "answer": "unconventional"
    },
    {
      "question": "in proportion  ",
      "answer": "proportionately"
    },
    {
      "question": "any decoration added as a trimming or adornment  ",
      "answer": "garnish"
    },
    {
      "question": "the sound of a step of someone walking",
      "answer": "footfall"
    },
    {
      "question": "the advancement of some enterprise",
      "answer": "forwarding"
    },
    {
      "question": "a cellar or vault or underground burial chamber (especially beneath a church)  ",
      "answer": "crypt"
    },
    {
      "question": "a workplace where fish are caught and processed and sold  ",
      "answer": "fishery"
    },
    {
      "question": "cause to grow together parts from different plants",
      "answer": "graft"
    },
    {
      "question": "more than necessary",
      "answer": "overmuch"
    },
    {
      "question": "feeling jolly and jovial and full of good humor  ",
      "answer": "jollity"
    },
    {
      "question": "curved into a half circle  ",
      "answer": "semicircular"
    },
    {
      "question": "a cocktail made of creme de menthe and cream (sometimes with creme de cacao)  ",
      "answer": "grasshopper"
    },
    {
      "question": "not held in chemical or physical combination  ",
      "answer": "unbound"
    },
    {
      "question": "that confounds or contradicts or confuses  ",
      "answer": "confounding"
    },
    {
      "question": "fail to catch, as of a ball  ",
      "answer": "muff"
    },
    {
      "question": "a plant adapted to arid conditions and characterized by fleshy water-storing tissues that act as water reservoirs  ",
      "answer": "succulent"
    },
    {
      "question": "move or pull with a sudden motion  ",
      "answer": "twitch"
    },
    {
      "question": "a bonus",
      "answer": "dividend"
    },
    {
      "question": "the quality of being alike",
      "answer": "sameness"
    },
    {
      "question": "requiring sitting or little activity",
      "answer": "sedentary"
    },
    {
      "question": "someone who makes or mends dresses  ",
      "answer": "dressmaker"
    },
    {
      "question": "ride a racehorse as a professional jockey  ",
      "answer": "jockey"
    },
    {
      "question": "divide or split up",
      "answer": "segment"
    },
    {
      "question": "(of a female body) healthily plump and vigorous ",
      "answer": "buxom"
    },
    {
      "question": "the quality of being adaptable or variable",
      "answer": "flexibility"
    },
    {
      "question": "having no living or known mother  ",
      "answer": "motherless"
    },
    {
      "question": "causing physical or especially psychological injury",
      "answer": "stabbing"
    },
    {
      "question": "a litter for transporting people who are ill or wounded or dead",
      "answer": "stretcher"
    },
    {
      "question": "an actor in a comedy  ",
      "answer": "comedian"
    },
    {
      "question": "excessively fat",
      "answer": "corpulent"
    },
    {
      "question": "a legal proceeding in a court",
      "answer": "litigation"
    },
    {
      "question": "punish by putting in a pillory  ",
      "answer": "pillory"
    },
    {
      "question": "having elegance or taste or refinement in manners or dress",
      "answer": "stylish"
    },
    {
      "question": "a series of acts at a night club  ",
      "answer": "cabaret"
    },
    {
      "question": "declare unavailable, as for security reasons",
      "answer": "classify"
    },
    {
      "question": "a list of acknowledgements of those who contributed to the creation of a film (usually run at the end of the film)  ",
      "answer": "credits"
    },
    {
      "question": "a document that must be accepted and paid by another person  ",
      "answer": "presentment"
    },
    {
      "question": "a union of interests or purposes or sympathies among members of a group  ",
      "answer": "solidarity"
    },
    {
      "question": "visual imagery  ",
      "answer": "picturing"
    },
    {
      "question": "a straight sword with a narrow blade and two edges  ",
      "answer": "rapier"
    },
    {
      "question": "an analysis into mutually exclusive categories  ",
      "answer": "breakdown"
    },
    {
      "question": "a volatile flammable mixture of hydrocarbons (hexane and heptane and octane etc.) derived from petroleum",
      "answer": "gasoline"
    },
    {
      "question": "a former United Kingdom silver coin",
      "answer": "twopence"
    },
    {
      "question": "exhibiting variation and change",
      "answer": "variant"
    },
    {
      "question": "an energetic style  ",
      "answer": "vitality"
    },
    {
      "question": "the quality of never making an error  ",
      "answer": "infallibility"
    },
    {
      "question": "take illegally",
      "answer": "loot"
    },
    {
      "question": "usually large pulpy deep-yellow round fruit of the squash family maturing in late summer or early autumn  ",
      "answer": "pumpkin"
    },
    {
      "question": "(medicine) a systematic plan for therapy (often including diet)  ",
      "answer": "regimen"
    },
    {
      "question": "a person who plays the piano  ",
      "answer": "pianist"
    },
    {
      "question": "undergo a chemical reaction",
      "answer": "react"
    },
    {
      "question": "the imposition of taxes",
      "answer": "taxation"
    },
    {
      "question": "a member of a municipal legislative body (as a city council)",
      "answer": "alderman"
    },
    {
      "question": "cut into filets",
      "answer": "fillet"
    },
    {
      "question": "dissolute indulgence in sensual pleasure  ",
      "answer": "profligacy"
    },
    {
      "question": "the necessary means (especially financial means)  ",
      "answer": "wherewithal"
    },
    {
      "question": "annoyed and irritable  ",
      "answer": "crabbed"
    },
    {
      "question": "in a plaintive manner",
      "answer": "plaintively"
    },
    {
      "question": "concern for your own interests and welfare  ",
      "answer": "egoism"
    },
    {
      "question": "move in an agitated or confused manner  ",
      "answer": "flurry"
    },
    {
      "question": "a cart for carrying small loads",
      "answer": "barrow"
    },
    {
      "question": "a person who eats human flesh  ",
      "answer": "cannibal"
    },
    {
      "question": "the act of regarding as equal  ",
      "answer": "equation"
    },
    {
      "question": "marked by materialism  ",
      "answer": "materialistic"
    },
    {
      "question": "not successful",
      "answer": "unsuccessful"
    },
    {
      "question": "Arctic deer with large antlers in both sexes",
      "answer": "caribou"
    },
    {
      "question": "not proportionate  ",
      "answer": "disproportionate"
    },
    {
      "question": "a complete change of physical form or substance especially as by magic or witchcraft  ",
      "answer": "metamorphosis"
    },
    {
      "question": "a system of scaffolds  ",
      "answer": "scaffolding"
    },
    {
      "question": "hit with the hand  ",
      "answer": "cuff"
    },
    {
      "question": "teach and impress by frequent repetitions or admonitions",
      "answer": "inculcate"
    },
    {
      "question": "of or relating to the stage or stage scenery",
      "answer": "scenic"
    },
    {
      "question": "a specialist assigned to the staff of a diplomatic mission  ",
      "answer": "attache"
    }
  ]
}